so uh he is God says
I have given you the freedom of
living or just living
whether you accept the revelation
or rejecting
guidance and the following
Logan
and that was to help
and God says
even among you
there is no proportion
but whoever believes
granted by God
and
so far
gives an example of Abraham
you are so determined
that this fall through
those eyes of worshiped
that you know God
bringing
comes from the best
scripted
as soon as they were in the beginning
and since the code is coming this is the
current verse the truth is
but the code it verifies every single
Ayah in this book
every letter
and so we don't have to guess and I
think it's like a forecasting a forecast
for the people of the four generations
and finale it's a it's a symbol of our
of our of victory
that one 257 I haven't observation
because God is the Lord of those who
believe
because he leads them out of the
darkness into the light
a thing
but when God did you out of the life you
see everything
you can actually feel the difference you
can feel that you know you just meet
people who don't have a good portion of
knowing or even in the Quran they will
see how ignorant they are for example
there's something possessed with someone
else you don't know what is going to
happen
what you are here for where we're going
what is the purpose of our life we just
don't know it's completely lost when you
see a person who's 65 years old but you
see that he has a baby so
feet
are those two lines also
a repetition
if we have a choice but then what is
turning it right around saying we don't
have a choice
that only those people who are supposed
to get the messages
yeah but that dress you have the freedom
of Joyce is a new decision to believe or
not to believe that decision is
absolutely the best of that decision
deliberately
so if you make a decision we don't have
anything to do with God the way it comes
down
if you make a decision to believe in God
all circumstances will work out to
direct you to the right path
now the rest of the verses why those who
disbelieve their Lords are their idols
they lead them out of the life into the
darkness
now we have a brother come here
who was studying the issues that we have
in this month and he decided to test my
translation and write comments on it and
he sat out there in the balcony and he
took a big notebook
he wrote down his comments and he had a
plan to come and try this a week ago or
two weeks ago to debate the issue with
me
they also went around the other mosques
to talk to them and explore
and then when he came across the
economic Center they told them oh no
don't don't go back and prevent the
issues
can tell us the story there
and he was really determined to come and
debate the issue but they want him to
stay in the dark they are afraid that he
may come across something that would
open his eyes and make him see the tools
of see the light
is that
and we were ready the Friday performed
last
and then all of a sudden it became very
excited
they convinced him not to talk to us
right well then he was supposed to call
me and then
I have been thriving for a few months
now to have them set time and a place
and their own terms to go on to get the
issues
well there
the people to stay in the dark you don't
want to discuss anything
and some of them said were afraid to him
what
happened
before
I think we're gonna we're gonna set a
reward
that's me the next step we'll see we're
going to have a reward for people to
come into better issues
I don't know how we can encourage them
I want them to have the place the time
their own terms
and it just doesn't work
but the verse here says that
they lead them out of the light into the
darkness
and certainly discussing the issues is
enlightenment
but if they want to keep them in the
dark they keep from the dark they don't
want to discuss over here
and
they're very important I know I know you
feel that you came out of the darkness
into your life
who said
death
to 100 years
you realize what happened because
now I know that God is able to do
anything
who died
is
God talking directly to the person
you've been speaking to him yeah
well I'm asking by the words he knows it
by the words
let's let's see um
would be uh
anything
so it doesn't say God said
the word father you know he said yeah
it's uh
it doesn't have the same definition
inspiration
delivering the question
oh yeah that's that's Abraham yeah
so he didn't speak forever
we know God does not speak forever
the one God spoke to Moses but Quran
makes a big issue out of it so
when God speaks to someone it's a big
thing as it had to be mentioned
specifically
so God's speaking to
ever even when Muhammad was taken to the
seventh heaven God did not speak to me
it is mentioned specifically that he was
inspired
we didn't spoke to them or not yeah
what's the big deal it doesn't make any
difference well speaking in the world
speaking can be effective
speaking can necessarily you know it
doesn't necessarily mean with a tongue
like you say here it implies that Allah
was speaking during this translation
is Maybe
just you just had a big discussion about
it we read the Quran
and so how we're
maybe we question things we don't need
to be questioning or maybe we're taking
a lot more out of something than we
should because of the way the English is
a question
however this is not important it really
is the important issue here is
how long does it for invest in this
election
Resurrection is one money
when you die you open your eyes the next
next morning and this video Resurrection
even if it was a million years
you were dead for millions of years
remember
how long was it
so much
see we all experienced death all right
we know how it feels like you know how
long it takes we know how aware of the
world is affair
s
no you were there
but you were dead
and when you die the second death
thank you
when you love the second test you're
going to miss the president of the
United States in the year 2000 and
2088 yeah
you don't care either
okay I'm not gonna be uh
now why do we have this verse in the
Quran what is the lesson that we derive
from that
that 100 years years past like one day
or half of the day
309 years passed like one day or part of
the day therefore the concept of time
disappeared